buyingcome.com 2013-08-06

# Terms - BuyingCome.com

## Privacy Policy

[buyingcome.com](http://www.buyingcome.com/) respects the privacy of your information. Our Privacy Policy governs our online information practices and reflects our commitment to protect your privacy.

**Security Measures:** Your account information and profile are password protected. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. Remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished your session.

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

**Information Collection and Use:** buyingcome.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We attempt to keep this information, apart from whatever information is used to market your company to potential trading partners, private. buyingcome.com does reserve the right to cooperate with law enforcement inquires and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property and other rights when, in its sole discretion, it believes in good faith such information is required to assist such parties.

**Public Access to Information:** The information you provide will be made available to all users of our website. Please remember that any information you disclose becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personally-identifying information.

**Disclosure of Information:** We reserve the right to disclose your information where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing (or threatening to infringe) or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our title, rights, interests or property or those of other website users or of anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.

We also reserve the rights to disclose, without notice to you, personal information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is required by any law, regulation or listing requirement or by any stock/securities exchange, governmental or regulatory authority.

**Cookies:** buyingcome.com may set and access cookies on your computer. buyingcome.com allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to buyingcome.com's cookies.

**Log Files:** We use IP addresses to obtain metrics, analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

**Changes to This Policy:** buyingcome.com may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
